Guide to the Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad Company Records, 1860-1999 AIS.1982.23
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Maps, Drawings and Plans, 1872-1990; XIV.; 593 items
  - Other Railroad Companies, 1882-1990; 3.
    - Monongahela Connecting Railroad Company (Roll 21)
      - Blueprint map of tracks from Thirty-fourth Street to the end, including location of oil storage tanks and other Jones & Laughlin buildings, January 1, 1929; 5.
      - Blueprint map of high and low grade tracks along Furnace Alley at Jones & Laughlin's Hazelwood Works, showing locations of blast furnaces and shops, January 1, 1929; 6.
      - Map of tracks from cupolas to No. 5 furnace along Furnace Alley at Jones & Laughlin's Hazelwood Works, showing locations of blast furnaces and shops, September 30, 1924; 7.
      - Blueprint general index map of Monongahela Connecting Railroad tracks, including Eastern Railroad tracks and showing location of Jones & Laughlin steel-works and other plants on both sides of the Monongahela River, January 1, 1929; 8. (Roll 22)
      - Blueprint map of tracks from Jones & Laughlin's Keystone Works to the Hot Metal Bridge, January 1, 1929; 9.
      - Blueprint map of tracks from Jones & Laughlin's Soho Works to its Keystone Works, showing location of various mills and other buildings, January 1, 1929; 10.
      - Blueprint map of tracks from Elba Junction to and through the roundhouse, showing location of National Tube Company's Continental Works and several old Jones & Laughlin coke ovens, January 1, 1929; 11.
      - Blueprint map of East Branch tracks, showing location of several Jones & Laughlin coke ovens and other J & L buildings, January 1, 1929; 12.
      - Blueprint map of East Branch and Eastern Railroad tracks, showing location of several Jones & Laughlin buildings, January 1, 1929; 13.
      - Blueprint map of Eastern Railroad tracks, showing location of several Jones & Laughlin buildings, January 1, 1929; 14.
      - Map of proposed changes to the Eastern Yard from Station 138+50 to Station 142+64, December 31, 1960; 15. (Roll 23)
      - General plan for No. 4 Open Hearth Furnace Plant, Jones & Laughlin Steel Corporation, Pittsburgh Works; Swindell-Dressler Corporation, Engineers; Includes Lyford Committee Recommended Switching Practices; Accompanied by 4 page report on operation and track ownership in No. 4 Open Hearth area, June 1, 1951; 16.
      - Map of the Monongahela Connecting Railroad tracks, including Jones & Laughlin steel-works on both side of the Monongahela River, with "Interstate Commerce Map" on verso, March 27, 1919; 17.
      - Map of the Eastern Yard, showing the location of a proposed diesel shop at the southern end, December 31, 1960; 18.
      - Map of the southern portion of the Eastern Yard, showing the locations of a proposed diesel shop and car repair yard, December 31, 1960; 19.
      - Right of way and track map of the Eastern Yard from Station 138+50 to Station 142+64, December 31, 1960; 20.
    - Monongahela Railways Company (Map-case 30-6, Folder 2)
    - Monongahela Railways Company (Roll 24)
    - Montour Railroad Company (Map-case 30-6, Folder 3)
      - National Mining Company Property, Jume 14, 1920
      - North Star Junction, undated
      - Right of Way and Track Map, August 20, 1990
      - Route Map, September 14, 1976
    - Montour Railroad Company (Roll 25-27)
    - New Castle Northern Railway Company (Roll 28)
    - Pittsburgh, Fort Wayne and Chicago Railway Company (Roll 29)
    - Pittsburgh, Lisbon and Western Railroad Company (Map-case 30-6, Folder 4)
    - Pittsburgh, McKeesport and Youghiogheny Railroad Company (Map-case 30-6, Folder 5)
      - Right of Way and Track Map, Sheet 6, December 13, 1969
      - Right of Way and Track Map, Sheet 7, December 13, 1969
    - Pittsburgh, McKeesport and Youghiogheny Railroad Company (Roll 30)
    - Youngstown and Suburban Railroad Company (Map-case 30-6, Folder 6)
      - Concrete Stone and Sand Company, April 13, 1931
    - Other Railroad Companies, A-Z (Map-case 30-6, Folder 7)
      - Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company Station Map, undated
      - Western Maryland Railroad Map, undated
  - Geographic Maps, 1872-1965; 4.
    - By Location, A-O (Map-case 30-6, Folder 8)
      - Road map of Beaver County, June 1946
      - Donora Works, 1965
      - Freedom Oil Works Property, 1893
      - Community of Moon Township and Monaca Borough, 1933
      - Roads and Groves in North Park, 1935
    - By Location, P-Z (Map-case 30-6, Folder 9)
      - Coursin Heights Plan of Lots, Situate in 10th Ward, McKeesport, Pennsylvania, December 1900
      - Lot Plan of North Webster, 1872
      - Rochester Tumbler Company, 1895
      - Borough of Rochester water lines, section 1 of 6, 1936
      - Borough of Rochester water lines, section 2 of 6, undated
      - Borough of Rochester water lines, section 3 of 6, 1936
      - Borough of Rochester water lines, section 4 of 6, 1936
      - Borough of Rochester water lines, section 5 of 6, 1936
      - Borough of Rochester water lines, section 6 of 6, 1936
      - Borough of Rochester deed layout, 1936
      - Ward No. 2, Rochester (Pa.), undated
      - Plan of Olive Stove Works in Rochester, 1911
      - Village of Webster and Gilmore's Farm, 1936
      - Principal Inland Waterways, Including Proposed Ohio River-Lake Erie Canal, 1936
      - Youngstown, Ohio, undated
    - By Location, A-Z (Roll 31)